Your cart is empty
------------------

Have an account?

[Log in](https://estesrockets.com/customer_authentication/redirect?locale=en&region_country=US) to check out faster.

Your cart
---------

Loading...

Subtotal
--------

$0.00

Taxes and [shipping](https://estesrockets.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout

Route is an added layer of protection to your order which insures replacement from lost, stolen, or damaged packages. By unselecting it, you are opting out of this premium feature.

Update

Check Out

* Rockets
    
    Rockets
    
    * By Skill Level
        
        By Skill Level

    * By Type
        
        By Type

    * By Line
        
        By Line

* Engines
    
    Engines
    
    * Size
        
        Size

    * Type
        
        Type

* Accessories
    
    Accessories
    
    * Building Supplies
        
        Building Supplies

    * Launch Supplies
        
        Launch Supplies

* Service
    
    Service

* Rockets
    
    * By Skill Level

    * By Type

    * By Line

* Engines
    
    * Size

    * Type

* Accessories
    
    * Building Supplies

    * Launch Supplies

* Service

 Search [Log in](https://estesrockets.com/customer_authentication/redirect?locale=en&region_country=US) [Cart](https://estesrockets.com/cart)

Privacy policy
==============

Our privacy policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and our customers’ needs.

At Estes Industries, LLC, we want you to enjoy our products and our website. We know your privacy during online visits is important to you, and this policy will tell you how and when we collect information through our website and how this information will be used.

We take online privacy and security concerns seriously. At the same time, we are continually working to make your personal experience when visiting our site as pleasant as possible. To help us accomplish that goal, we will need to collect and use some information from you when you use our site. We utilize appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information. Credit card information is processed through a secure, reliable well-known gateway.

All of the websites under the estesrockets.com domain may collect information from you – personal as well as non-personal – for internal use within Estes Industries, LLC.

**The Information We Collect:**

This pertains to all information collected or submitted on the estesrockets.com websites. On some pages, you can create an account, order products, make requests, and register to receive materials such as newsletters. The types of personal information collected on these pages are:

Name

Address

Email

Address

Phone Number

Credit Card Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you place an order, and the billing address is different from the shipping address, then you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name

Address

Phone Number

In some instances, we may need to disclose personal information about you to companies that we hire so that we may provide you with the best possible service; for example we would need to share your address with a company we employ to deliver your order. We may also disclose personal information to reputable research companies to conduct customer surveys. However, such companies will be under an obligation to keep your personal information confidential.

We may disclose personal information collected from you as required by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a specific request from a law enforcement agency.

Also, please note, the application of our privacy policy is limited to residents of the United States. Further, Estes Industries, LLC may provide links to other websites. This privacy policy does not apply to other websites and the personal information they may collect.

Except as set out above, we will not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose any personal information to any company or person outside of Estes Industries, LLC, without obtaining appropriate permission prior to such disclosure.

We may collect information about you and your interests also on our site for our own purposes through both active and passive means. We collect personal information directly from you through our sites when you contact us through our site, when you create an account, and when you purchase products. We also use passive means to collect some information, such as tracking which pages you go to on the site. We use this information in order to determine how to make your experience at our sites more enjoyable.

We will not use personal information we collect from you for purposes other than those for which the information was collected without asking for appropriate permission prior to such use.

You have the right to review any personal information we may have concerning you. Please contact us to request your information.

We cannot and will not establish conditions that will require or encourage anyone to disclose personal information over and above what is reasonably necessary to participate in any activity featured on our websites and pages.

**Purchasing from estesrockets.com**

You must be 18 years of age or older to purchase.

When you make a purchase from estesrockets.com, we will need to obtain personal information from you. We will need your real name and address (billing as well as shipping addresses) along with your credit card information or other payment method in order to complete your transaction and ship your products.

If you are age 18 or over, you can choose to set up an online account with us to use for purchasing products from estesrockets.com, in which account we will keep all information relating to your purchases even after your transaction is completed. This will make it even easier for you to shop with us again because you won’t need to submit such information each time. You can review and update your online account information at any time. If you decide to set up an account with us, we will ask you to create a username and password, which will ensure that you are the only one who can access your account.

**Does estesrockets.com use cookies?**

Yes. When you create an account, we add a cookie to your computer (unless your system is set up not to receive cookies), in order to help us keep track of what features you use and what products you may buy. We also add the cookie in order to remember your browser settings, such as the type of browser you use and what plug ins you have installed. This keeps us from bothering you every time you enter the site in order to make sure that you have the necessary equipment. It also allows us to know how many people are using certain features so that we can adjust our site to provide the best browsing experience for every visitor. When we add a cookie, we are not collecting personal information, but the non-personal information that helps us make sure that our products and our communications to our guests are responsive to their interests.

**What is a cookie?**

Cookies are small data files that your browser may place on your computer when you visit different websites to mark that you have been there.

**How do I know when a cookie has been added?**

Check your settings. Many browsers allow you to choose your preferences. If you have set your browser settings to refuse cookies, we cannot put a cookie on your computer.

**What if I don’t accept the cookie?**

If an estesrockets.com cookie is not present, it will limit our ability to customize our site for you, deliver a better online experience, and improve the features of our site. Some cookies save us from having to check for compatibility of your system with various parts of the site every time you visit, making the site faster and easier for you to use. If you don’t accept our cookies, you won’t be able to add items to your wishlist, and the site will be a little slower as we check your browser’s compatibility with our site as you click through.

**How do I change or review the information in my account?**

Personal information collected online from you may be reviewed by accessing your online account. Customers who have set up an online account with us may update their account information and change personal options at any time.

Estes continues to ignite the imagination of each new generation with industry-leading model rocketry products and education.

### Connect with us on social media!

### Connect with us on social media!

###### Customer Service

###### Estes Industries

###### Shop Rockets

© 2024, Estes Rockets

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.

 Purchase options

Select a purchase option to pre order this product

Countdown header  
Countdown message

DAYS

:

HRS

:

MINS

:

SECS

Adding free gift to the cart...
